> > Jem Young: 好的，这样很好，像我说的，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right, so
that that's fine and nginx, like I said,
是一个网络服务器
it's a web server.
因此，我们可以为静态 HTML 页面和所有这些页面提供服务。
So we can serve static HTML pages and
all that.
但在某个时候，我们想创造复杂的应用。
But at some point,
we wanna create complex applications.
具有不同路径的应用程序，
Applications that have different paths,
不同的方法可以连接到数据库
different ways of maybe
connect to a databas.
只是编码，更像我们每天所做的。
Just coding, kind of more akin
to what we do in our day to day.
为此，我们将创建应用程序服务器。
To do that,
we're gonna create an application server.
这与 Web 服务器不同。
And that's different from a web server.
而网络服务器只接收了大量的网络流量
And the web server's just
receiving a lot of web traffic and
做点什么
doing something with it.
应用程序正在执行所有重型提升。
The application is doing
all the heavy lifting.
对于我们今天的申请，我们将使用 NodeJS。
For our application today
we're gonna use NodeJS.
我的网站是用 Python 构建的，但我今天不会走那条路。
My website is built in Python using Flask,
but I won't go that route today.
让我们做 NodeJS ，因为我们大多数人都知道 JavaScript ，我在假定。
Let's do NodeJS because, well,
most of us know JavaScript, I'm assuming.
如果不是的话 NodeJS 有很多课程
If not,
there's a lot of courses on NodeJS,
将添加到将来的链接。
will add links to those in the future.
我们将更多地了解到 NodeJS 的详细信息，但对于
And we'll get more into more
details into NodeJS but for
现在我想创造最基本的网络服务器
now I wanna create
the most basic web server.
>> Jem Young: 什么是 NodeJS ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What is NodeJS though?
有人能告诉我是什么吗
Can someone tell me just like what it is?
这只是一个简单的问题
And it seems like a really
simple question but
如果你问一个简单的问题，那就是运行 JavaScript的事情。
if you're asked a simple questions you're,
it's that thing that runs JavaScript.
NodeJS 是什么 ?
What is NodeJS?
>> 扬声器 2: 服务器端的 JavaScript 环境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: JavaScript environment for
the server side.
> > Jem Young: 我会接受的，对，对，对。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'll take that,
yeah, yeah, that's right.
>> 扬声器 2: 是，但它也是对
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, that but
it's also a binding for
Google 为 Chrome 开发的 V8 引擎。
the V8 engine that Google developed for
Chrome.
>> Jem Young: 是。 >> 扬声器 2: 它是最重要的
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's one of the most
性能刚刚好的 LLVM 编译器
performant just-in-time
LLVM compilers out there.
> > Jem Young: 是的，每个人都有正确的比特，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, everybody had
bits of it correct and altogether,
我们都是对的很好这就是我们在一个过程中的原因
we're all right, which is good,
that's why we're in a course.
好的，它本质上只是一个在 V8 之上运行的 JavaScript 引擎，
All right, it is essentially just a
JavaScript engine that runs on top of V8,
是 Google Chrome开发的
which is developed by Google Chrome.
通常是几个版本，所以
It's usually a few versions behind, so
Chrome 具有节点尚未实际支持的功能。
Chrome has features that Node
doesn't actually support yet.
但是本质上它是一个单线程的 JavaScript 引擎
But essentially, it's a single threaded
JavaScript engine that executes
JavaScript 并且可以处理请求，即它。
JavaScript and
can handle requests, that's it.
这条线索就像我们工程师一样
The single thread in this is
something that as we engineers,
我们可能不喜欢
we probably don't appreciate.
所以这意味着如果请求来了
So, that means if a request comes in,
它可以非常非常好的处理异步的事情。
it can handle things being
asynchronous very very very well.
所以我们可以用这个 JavaScript λ，当然是请求块。
So much so that we can use that JavaScript
Lambda, of course request on block.
但在 Python 或 Java 或大多数其他语言请求块中。
But in Python or Java or
in most other languages request block.
所以这意味着如果我对一个非常大的图像文件发出一个请求
So that means if I make a single
request for a very large image file,
这是我不知道伦敦要花时间的
and that's a fetching from, I don't know,
London, it's gonna take time.
这意味着任何其他的请求都会被阻止
And that means every other request
that comes in is gonna get blocked,
等待其他请求解决与运行节点的问题。
waiting for the other requests to
resolve versus running a node.
节点是异步的，它说，嘿，我想得到这个图像。
Node is asynchronous, it says,
hey, I wanna get this image.
我要去拿这幅照片
I'm gonna go get this image,
in the meantime,
我要去处理其他的要求
I'm gonna go handle all
these other requests.
这就是所谓的事件循环，不断地不停地运行
And that's what's known as the event loop,
is just constantly running over and
说，有什么事吗 ?
saying like, is there anything to do?
有什么事吗
Is there anything to do?
那是一个很强大的概念
That's a really powerful concept,
你可能不喜欢用语言来交换语言
you probably won't appreciate
it to switch languages.
你是在处理拦截请求
And you're you're dealing
with blocking requests,
你得处理好申请钥匙之类的事
you have to handle request keys and
things like that.
而节点仅能无缝地处理这一问题。
Whereas Node just handles that seamlessly.
这就是为什么节点通常是我在创建 Web 服务器时的首选项
That's why Node is usually my go-to when
it comes to creating a web server cuz
它只会处理好的事情
it just handles things really well.
最快吗 ?
Is it the fastest?
不， Java 通常是更快的，或者 Go 或 Rust。
No, Java is generally gonna be faster or
Go or Rust.
或者很多其他语言，不是最快的语言。
Or many other languages,
it's not the fastest languages.
但如果有人想讨论你的问题
But if anybody wants to nerd debate you,
which people do,
就是有我需要的人
just be, Node does what I need.
大部分时间你都不会被引擎的速度限制
And most of the time you're not gonna
be limited by the speed of the engine
正在运行。
that is running.
就像你写的代码一样
It's gonna be something else,
like the code you wrote.
你会在某个时候听到关于什么更好特别是
You will at some point gonna hear
a debate about what's better, especially,
如果你能和 C 开发者说话之类的话
if you get to talking to C developers and
things like that.
对不起，这是一个正切，让我们安装节点。
Sorry, that was a tangent,
let's install Node.
[LAUGH] 我们将与 npm一起安装 NodeJS 。
[LAUGH] We're gonna install
NodeJS along with npm.
因此， sudo 适合安装 nodejs npm，因此请同时安装这两个节点。
So sudo apt install nodejs npm, so
install both of them at the same time.
> > Jem Young: 所以我要继续做这个， sudo apt。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So I'm gonna go ahead and
do that, sudo apt.
>> Jem Young: 是。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes.
>> Jem Young: 如果您想知道为什么我说 NodeJS 而不是 Node，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: If you're wondering
why I said NodeJS and not Node,
节点最初是 Linux 的无线应用。
Node originally was a radio
application for Linux.
在最长的时间内，如果已安装节点，那么它将安装此应用程序。
For the longest time, if you installed
Node it would install this application.
但人们对这一问题感到非常不满
But people got really annoyed
at it because they're,
使用此与使用节点的人数对比的人员吗 ?
who uses this versus the number
of people that use Node?
现在只是 NodeJS ，如果我输入节点，它就会接管，
So now it's just NodeJS and
it's gonna take over, if I type in Node,
它会用这个
it's gonna use that.
在先前版本的类中，实际上有一个符号链接它。
In the previous version of the class
actually had a symbolic link it back.
因此，我将符号链接指向实际的 NodeJS
So I make a symbolic link
to the actual NodeJS so
节点等于节点 JS，而不是每次输入 NodeJS 。
Node equals Node JS,
rather than typing NodeJS every time.
内德 - 特里维娅没必要知道但我们在 JavaScript里有了很长的路
Nerd trivia, didn't need to know, but
we've come a long way in JavaScript.
有一段时间，节点被向下看，是 JavaScript 的后端。
There's a time when Node was looked down,
it's, JavaScript's for the back end.
现在 Netflix 运行，我不会完全在节点上说，但是
Now Netflix runs,
I won't say entirely on Node, but
主要在节点和 JavaScript上运行。
runs largely on Node and JavaScript.
其他部分以多种语言编写，大部分是 Java。
With other parts written in
various languages, mostly Java.
但别让任何人给你胡说胡话
But don't let anybody give you crap,
if they talk about Node,
这就是我要说的
that's all I'm saying.
我们已经完成了我也要安装 Git
And we're done, and
I'm gonna install Git, too.
它通常是在缺省情况下安装的，但这是将来的自我证明。
It's usually installed by default,
but this is future-proofing ourselves.
哎呀，忘了 sudo， sudo apt install git.
So oops, forgot the sudo,
sudo apt install git.
它通常已经安装了但就用在箱子里
And it's usually installed already,
but just in case,
我们会确保 Git 的安装
we'll make sure Git is installed.
>> Jem Young: 因此，只需为我们的版本控制安装 git 。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So just apt install git for
our version in control.